

□ (+60) 14-881-7836 | **S** barlowy@protonmail.com | **©** kmacod | **m** kmacod

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary ₋

Currently a software engineer at Binary.com. With 2+ years of experience working as a web developer, Brandon is a versatile, analytical and hardworking young professional with a passion in software and self improvement. Ready to work with and learn from anyone.

Skills

Languages Javascript, Python

Tooling Git, Bash, Linux, Mobx, Lerna, grunt/gulp, npm/yarn, ... various other JS libaries

Frameworks React, Django, Django Rest Framework, Flask, Scrapy

Industry Knowledge CI/CD, Agile Software Development

Work Experience _____

Binary Group Services Sdn. Bhd.

Cyberjaya, Malaysia

Jul. 2017 - Jun. 2018

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Dec. 2018 - Present

- Learned the Javascript/Frontend ecosystem without prior experience or exposure.
- · Worked in a team and inter-department environment to deliver thorough and detailed work without cutting corners.
- Built and maintained large and complex code bases used by millions of people.
- Translate design and wire frames into code.
- · Maintained our legacy projects by squashing bugs, resolving security issues and perform required amendments to it.
- Participated in scrum related activities to ensure proper software development lifecycle.

Freelance Remote

• Implemented RESTful API server for a invoice tracking system.

- Collaborated with remote teams to deliver the product.
- Helped to implement a redesign on a social media management service.
- Built a shopify shop for a local car rental.

Projects

Deriv App

Frontend

JAVASCRIPT (ES5, ES6), REACT, MOBX, WEBPACK, SASS, LERNA

- · Single Page Application built using React, JSX, and Mobx, which features a charting library used to display financial and market data, built to replace Binary Static.
- · Collaborated with other departments in a team based environment to deliver new features and maintain the application.

Binary Static Frontend

JAVASCRIPT (ES5, ES6), JSX, WEBPACK, SASS, JQUERY

Dec. 2018 - Present

Dec 2018 - Present

- · A legacy trading application built using jQuery and minimal JSX as its templating system, with a big and complex code base.
- · Helped maintained the application by fixing security issue, squashing bugs and performing required ammendments while also occasionally add new features to it.

Education

Riam Road Secondary School

Miri, Malaysia Jan. 2014 - Dec. 2016

MALAYSIAN CERTIFICATE OF EXAMINATION

- The Malaysian Certificate of Examination is the equivalent of the GCSE in England or GCE Ordinary Level in the Commonwealth of Nations.
- Scored a 3A 4B in the examination which includes Mathematics (A-), Science (A), English (A), Malay (B+), Moral Studies (B+), History (B), and Art
- The English subject has 2 results, one is the MCE result and the other is the GCE Ordinary Level result, in which I scored an A as well.

MARCH 19, 2020 BRANDON YII · RÉSUMÉ